The.
A listen.
The. Number.
The the way.
The the.
New. The new.
Moon will.
Be the.
The old.
Girl. A song.
Stuff.
A lawyer.
They had to make again the time change the
first day in something well that well at
eight o'clock and it's still light on
a good the extra day Why
does US Now we've still got
a three hour drive back we're not going
to be home until after midnight or if it
really bugs you John he would do it
and I don't want to blow something on
a scene like this you know I figure we're
either going to have to move mother out
here or move the grave in the
Pittsburgh she can't make
a trip like this. Sorry it clearly left.
You know what if this thing we still
remember I don't know I don't even remember
what the man looks like Johnny it takes
him five minutes you have five minutes to
put the wreath on the grave and six hours
to drive back and forth father wants to
remember so we truck two hundred miles
into the country and she stays at home we
would hear John all right if.
Coming after destruction. Of.
That telegraph the radio system in
the station which role was it in.
When there's no hour. Late. You've got
numbers in your outlook I already lost in
our sleep last time I think you
complain just you still talks dairies.
I wonder what happened to the one from last
year. Each year we spend good money on
these things we come out here in the one
from last years go all the flowers die and
the caretaker somebody takes them away and
a little spit and polish can clean this
up. Salad next year wonder how many times
we bought the same one.
They come on Barb church was this morning.
A I mean praying for church. I
haven't seen you in church lately.
Not much sense in my going to church. Do
you remember one time when we were small
we were out here it was for right over
there I jumped out at you from behind
a tree and grandpa got all excited he shook
his fist at me and he said boy you know
. Remember that right over there.
Where you say really be scared here.
Johnny. You're still afraid
stop it now I mean it.
Back to get you. Stop it you are
ignorant they're coming for
you. Stop it you're acting like
a child they're coming for you.
There comes one of them now.
He'll hear you. I'm
getting out of Germany.
The first.
Live.
Live
live. Live.
Live.
Live live.
live Live.
Live
.
I am.
So.
I. Should.
All right. Don't worry
about him like you have to
be
a lot more listeners and find
out about us. Truckers I guess
this point my view is like is there any we
can try to do and if we get some gas is
there any.
Suppose you try this.
Do you live here.
Geez.
We've got to get out. We have
to get where this other people.
May we're going to take some food
and see if I can find some food.
Good.
Thank you. Thank. You.
Thank. Happening. Why does have.
To look. There are
two of them out there as you see any more
around here I can take you I know I know
you are free.
Oh.
The it was. The of.
The air.
The
OK OK.
Thank you.
OK And oh.
Good. Look at it.
A few.
Years. Old.
It is.
oh Oh.
Yes that's what I saw this house.
Thank you. Why don't you see if you can
find somebody with some board something
about five years something
we've never faced.
Got. From the UK. I know you're afraid
I'm afraid too. But we have to try to avoid
the House of it now I'm going to board
up the windows and doors you understand
will be all right here we'll be all right
here to someone comes to rescue us but we
have to work together you'll have to help
me and I want you to go in and get
some wood so I think boy the place you
understand OK OK
. Good.
Oh no no no
no.
No
.
That's the wrong. Question misbegotten
because once you can find.
This room looks pretty secure. If we
have to we can run in here and going to
those. For the long fifty three
back hounding the way in here
right now. This very bizarre.
Place back out Colby happens.
And you know that's for sure I
have. This radio on the truck.
I jumped in to listen to it. And
a big gasoline truck came screaming right
across the road with must have been ten
fifteen of those things chasing
after. Grabbing and holding on.
I didn't see them at first. I could
just see that the truck was moving in
a funny way. Because things
were catching up to me. And
I quote right across the road. Slammed
are great people to get myself.
Right through the guardrail. I
guess. Is the driver has to come off the
road into that gas station by Beekmans
done. The right one bill boy
regular gas pump never stop moving
but out of our own moving
bonfire. Did not truck
was going to explode what. Still is man
screaming. This thing is just
backing away from it. I
look back to Dinah to see.
If there was anyone there who
could help me. When I knows that.
The entire place it encircled. Wasn't
a sign of life left except.
I know there were no
more screams. I. Realized that. I
was alone with fifty or sixty of
those things just. Standing there.
Staring at. I thought
I started to drive I.
Just plowed right through them. They
didn't move they didn't run or.
Just stood there staring at me.
I just wanted to crush them.
They. Scattered through the air like bugs.
We were riding in the cemetery.
Johnny in the. Tiny.
We. We came to put
a wreath on my father's grave. Charge him.
And he said. Can I have
some candy Barbara.
And we didn't have any. And.
Only. It's hot in here hot thanks.
And he said always late why did
we start so late and I said
Johnny if you had gotten up
earlier we wouldn't be late.
Johnny asked me if I were afraid.
And I said I'm not afraid Johnny.
And then this man started walking
up the road. He came slowly
and Johnny kept teasing me and saying he's
governing need get you Barbara. And I
laughed at him and said Johnny
stop it. And then Johnny ran away.
Like. I want to this man and I was
going to apologize. Why don't you just
keep calm and I looked up.
And I said could be. Any
grabbing me you. Didn't
Graham. How do you.
Find goods I think you just got out.
You know you really. Did the job they
came and you were and then just here
he thought this man and. I got
so brave I really am I right.
Jolly didn't come. We've got.
We have to wait for Johnny.
Maybe we better go out and get him. We
have to go out and get Johnny he's out
there. Please don't you hear me
we've got to go out and get me I'm.
Just we have to bolt that
job you. Do you like this.
Book you know what's going on out there
there's no Sunday School picnic all chill
on the stand my brother is oh my
goodness oh my God I know that dad.
Oh oh oh.
Because of the obvious threat to untold
numbers of citizens and because of the
crisis which is even now developing this
radio station will remain on the air day
and night the station and
hundreds of other radio and T.V.
Stations throughout this part of the country
are pooling their resources through an
emergency network up to keep you informed
of all developments at this hour these
are the facts as there is an epidemic
of mass murder being committed by
a virtual army of unidentified assassins
the murders are taking place in villages
cities homes and with parent or reason
for the slayings it seems to be
a sudden general explosion of mass homicide
we have some descriptions. I would say
they are. Some of the appear to be in
a kind of trance others
describe them as being.
So but there is no way for us to say who
or what to look for yourself when you know
this monsters reaction upon Foresman officials
is one of complete people but that's
not so far. The name could determine any
kind of organized under way at least.
An emergency and humans who are literally.
Seen to be described as being of beers
with. Me with the governors
of. Those two states. GUARD
me any moment that is not happening as you
know only at least the reporters have
been able to get from official sources
its predecessors to stay in there behind
locked doors not venturing outside any
recent nature of this crisis. And until we
can find or start to see. This
crisis develops for thousands of office
and factory. Workers are being urged to
stay at their place of employment not to
make any attempt to get to their homes
however in spite of this urging and
warning streets and highways part with.
Any. Action at this stage.
The gentleman we just. Saw. Which is
the eastern third of. Maine within the
members of the president's cabinet.
Wish to be his. Conference
to be an official announcement as soon as
possible that this is the latest dispatch
just received in our newsroom. Latest
word also from national press services in
Washington D.C.
Al tells us that the emergency presidential
conference which you just mentioned let
me quote high ranking scientists from
the National Aeronautics and Space
ministration.
Join their facilities in an emergency effort
to bring you this news as it develops
we urge you to stay
tuned to Radio and T.V.
And to stay indoors at all costs reports
reaching this news room hello frightened
people seeking refuge in churches schools
and government buildings demanding
shelter and protection from the murder
which apparently is involving much of the
nation was. Clean even that
isn't even Iraq as well
as people.
Saying you know history no longer
and longer tours when there was
a time we don't know what kind
of murder had been you're.
The only Anyone who's.
Like they're going to.
Look at the. News or go with.
Well with. Other cities in the.
Eastern portion of Texas similar killings
have been reported around the Houston and
Galveston areas but nothing like
a family gone and some bullets out there.
Something like when these came clear we
were facing some kind of national emergency
when first reports began filtering in
usenet and law enforcement agencies
are of the opinion surprising voted
a pretty solid nature.
To be all right here for
a while tragically soon there and we haven't
gotten more police food and radio to
get
a suspect in up skewered kind of conspiracy
sooner or later someone says about the
coming get us out creatures or space so
again we joined with law enforcement
agencies urging you to seek shelter in
a building locked doors and windows and
that's as we know right any special thanks
to your radio and television for survival
instructions and for the details of this
continuing story but I don't know if you're
here yet many I'm going upstairs now so
if they try to break in here I can hear
from up there I'll be down to take care of
its cover. Beauty is everything is all right
from the back to reinforce the windows
and doors later but you're
right from the OK. OK.
Civil defense officials in Cumberland have
told newsman that murder victims show
evidence of having been partially
devoured by their murderers.
Consistent reports from witnesses to the
effect that people who acted as though
they were in
a kind of trance were killing and eating
their victims prompted authorities to
examine the bodies of some of the victims
medical authorities in Cumberland have
concluded that in all cases the killers
are eating the flesh of the people they
murdered repeating this latest bulletin
just received moments ago from Cumberland
Maryland civil defense authorities have
told news men that murder victims show
evidence of having been partially devoured
by their murderous medical examination
of victims' bodies shows conclusively that
the killers are eating the flesh of the
people they kill. So this incredible story
becomes more ghastly with each report
it's difficult to imagine such
a thing actually happening but these are
the reports we have been receiving and
passing on to you reports which have been
verified as completely as is possible in
this confused situation is happening and
it would appear that no one is safe from
this wave of news.
Just. Like we are from top city
radio County Pennsylvania but.
Parts of murder victims being partially
eaten by their Slayers is true no further
details available at this time however
my guys moved out there I could use some
help here that's
a sign it's the safest place you know you
didn't hear. Here always of course you
know what was going on in those things
probably your background was free nation or
group three thousand I vote based on where
you know I know them better you know how
just in time are you was going off
on a twenty we thought we did hear
a scream to keep growing you couldn't have
those things with us afterwards and you
would come up with Hello
Well if there were more of
a record sound like the places being ripped
apart how are we supposed to know what
was going on and well we're place but you
just got through saying you could hear
not use it how likely is this new group
or it would be nice to get your story
straight man all right you tell me. I don't
take that kind of a chance we've got
a safe place we're looking to
a safe place and you're telling us we've
got to risk our lives just because
somebody might need help Yes I'm OK
All right why don't we settle this
a sister we take up OK we're air corridors
now I suggest we all go back downstairs
before any of those things if I were in
here here hopeless or good I wouldn't care
if I was upstairs there will be hope for
you Lori same sours the same place I'm
telling you that you can't get in here and
I'm telling you the last things turned
over our car we were damn lucky to go at
all now you tell me those those things can
get through this law some power we're going
to. So wife and kids downstairs kids
her daughters who are still bigger
better are here and we could strengthen
everything up Mr Cooper was all of us we're
going to fix this place up and go tell
you everything we do up here we can take
all that stuff downstairs with us and
you're really crazy you
know let you get up
a million with us up here all these windows
are going up you can make them strong
enough to keep the Sens out I told you those
things don't have the strength I smash
three other men to push them out or not the
dollars to hear me when I told you late
hurdler our car will tell you the five
minute to do that that's my point on there
is not going to be five or even ten
or getting twenty thirty maybe
a hundred of those things and as soon as
they know we're here this place is going
to be crawling with of of that many they'll
probably get us wherever we go. Bulk
the seller the cellar there's only one door
right just one door that's all we have
to protect five business or Luxembourg
from the inside but up here all these
windows white we never know where they
were going to hit us next you've got
a point Mr Cooper but down in the cellar
there's no place to run to I mean given
they did get it there be no back exit will
be done before. We can get out here if
we have to and we don't want to see what's
going on outside but down there the wind
is the rescue party did come it wouldn't
even dulled the sour is the strongest
place to sell as
a dam stragglers I don't know who's to
Coburg I think it's rather. You know how
many is out there. Maybe six or seven
bucks. You two can do whatever you like but
I'm going back down to the cellar and you
Birdie side as up more of that door and
I'm not a law again I robbers Now wait
a minute Mr corral I'm not going to wait
I made my decision I can make yours now
wait
a minute let's think about this we can make
it to the cellar if we have to work and
if we do decide to stay down there will
need some things from up here so let's at
least consider this
a while yet. If you box yourself in
the seven those things get in the
house you've had it at
least up here you have
a fighting chance. Oh yeah
it looks like about eight or
ten of them now he swore they were. There
a lot out back to. The
.
I.
Guess it's the sports your crazy. Things
are going to get everyone on or in this
place we got shut down.
I'm taking the girl was really hurt here
your hands off and everything else that's
up here too because if I stay up here I'm
fighting for everything up here in the
radio and the food is part of what I'm
fighting for now you're going down the
cellar to get them and saying he's insane
we we've got to have fun down here we've
got to write this your house we've got all
right you got to do with him well yes or
no this is your last chance no beating
around the bush Let's listen I got
a kid down there she she can't play I
couldn't bring right here she can't possibly
take all right those those things flashing
through the windows Well her father if
you're stupid enough to go die in that
trap that's your business however I am not
stupid enough to follow
you it is tough with
a kid the old man is so stupid now you get
the hell down in the cellar you can be
the boss down there I'm
boss up here he passes.
You know I want to open this door and I
meet Mr Coburn with your help we get
a list of my help let him go man whose
mind is made up just let him gold.
Why did. Johnny Maharani.
I want to get her help I'm sorry.
But we stick together man and we can take
some really good. Lots of places we can
run to up here. This is
cool we're going to be
a lot better off of three
of us working together. A
good.
It's wrong. I'm not
a boxing myself and on the. Day like.
Now we're safe now it's boarded up tight
What about Tom and Judy and I want to stay
up there
a lot of. There are two
other people upstairs man and
a girl we usually screen. Yet I didn't
know who they were and I wasn't about to
take any unnecessary
chances of course not.
She all right I don't know why. She
feels warm maybe in shock or if you get
a bandage some laundry in
a basket and I should. Let
them stay up stairs. But. Too
many ways of monsters can get
in up there we'll see who's right. Will
see when they come begging me to let them
in down here that's important isn't it
ought to be writing about how to be wrong
what do you mean by that. There's
anyone out there know why we're
being attacked. Whatever it is it isn't
just happening here as some kind of mass
murder is going on everywhere radio said
to stay inside any of. Radio upstairs I
heard a new school there's
a radio upstairs and you border this in
down here and I know what I'm doing but did
it say nothing they don't know anything
about the mass murder everywhere and people
are supposed to look for
a safe place to hide take the boards off
that door we are staying here Helen Parry
They have radio with at least some kind
of communication if the authorities know
what's happening with those stand people
for us so the challenge of what to do how
are we going to know what's going on
if we are thousand of them gently.
And. We may not enjoy living together.
But dying together isn't going to solve
anything those people are enemies.
They're. OK. It's cool
Tom. If you would come downstairs for
a few minutes Harry and I could
come up stairs All right.
If we do it's going to look funny nothing
is going to be done with dinner most of
your. Do this for me. OK open
up.
Out care. And. Don't.
Stick.
To. The books you.
Are going to tell just.
So.
So don't be afraid.
I haven't cooked carrots why.
This place is ridiculous
look at this there's
a million weak spots up
here. Any one of those.
Have spread it was killed.
And they talk about the way those. I can
see I didn't think there could be fifty
million of those things out there
that's like with these windows are.
Why don't you do something
to help somebody.
Drag a couple of those
chairs to go there's
a side here. Are you
but everybody else who are gone I
was like Elias is there anything
not to live here anymore from Mr if you're
there you take your stuff and do their
goal it's our it's our out
there in our south. It.
Credible as they seem are not the
results of mass hysteria that.
All of us actually watch. Wave of murder
which is whipping the eastern third of the
nation is being committed by creatures who
feast upon the flesh of their victims
first eyewitness accounts of this grisly
development came from people who were
understandably like almost incoherent
officials and news men first discounted
those eyewitness descriptions as being
beyond belief however reports of persistent
medical examinations of some of the victims
or out the fact that they had been
partially devoured. I think we have some
late word just arriving and interrupt to
bring this to you. This is
the latest disclosure in
a report from National Civil Defense
headquarters in Washington. It has been
established that persons who have recently
died F been returning to life and
committing acts of murder. Widespread
investigation of reports from human homes
morgues and hospitals has concluded that
the UN buried dead are coming back to life
and seeking human victims. It's hard for
us here to believe what we're reporting to
you but it does seem to be
a fact. When this emergency first began
radio and television was inviting people to
stay inside behind locked doors for safety
that situation has now changed we are
able to report
a definite course of action. Civil defense
machinery has been organized to provide
rescue stations with food shelter medical
treatment and protection by armed
National Guardsman to stay to the broadcasting
stations and your local area will
just list
a rescue station just list to be repeated
throughout our news coverage look for the
name of the rescue station nearest you.
Make your way to that location as soon as
possible so we have the trucks we can
get some gas we can get out of here and
there's
a contract that shows I know that's why
I pulled in here but his last call this
afternoon by the president since convening
this conference of the presidential
cabinet the F.B.I.
Joint Chiefs of Staff CIA has not produced
any public information why our space
expert being consulted about an earthbound
emergency so far all the betting on the
answer to that question centers on the
recent Explorer satellite shot to Venus.
That satellite you recall started back to
Earth but never got here that's the space
vehicle which over to Venus and then print
was purposely destroyed by NASA when
scientists discovered it was carrying
a mysterious high level radiation with.
Could that radiation be somehow responsible
for the wholesale murders we're now
suffering. Newsman John Quinn Washington I
suppose those questions are best move to
try to get out of here how are you going
to get over that at the White
book because you're coming from
a meeting regarding the explosion of the
penis preservation Yes Yes That was
a subject of the meeting you feel there is
a connection between this and the
predominant there's a definite connection
a definite connection whether you feel
that the radiation on the Venus brothers
enough to call these cause these me tell
you is a very high degree of radiation
a minute I'm not sure that that's certain
Oh I don't think that even when you're
going to need to make sure we have this.
Procedure mysterious The radiation is not
the cause of the mutation I can't speak
for the entire military at this time
gentleman. Mr Grey with these gentlemen
presently until we do this is
a reputedly proof everything is being
done that can be done to her actually.
Professor you feel that there is
a definite connection between that connection
as far as Dr Keller and myself talk
to her please I I thought we decided that
is not proof yet was it when one of the
satellites when the satellite was exploding
usual amount of radiation enough to
cause me chasing under certain circumstances
could have perhaps been very honest it
does seem to have a bearish will there be
a. Strobe light or reply
yes later this afternoon.
There was really like every forty seconds
a group perhaps there were.
Later. Everything possible saw.
That the hoping to get further explanation
we read all we know we have to try to go
here he said The rest is the essence of the
office and medical supplies. Have been
hell for one of the world's foremost
authority. Shy of technology or.
Will it in
a moment it's only about seventeen miles
from. You know these are you from around
here Julian are both from around here
we were on our way up to the lake to go
swimming and Julie had
a radio and we heard the first reports about
this so we knew the old house was here
and we came in and found the lady upstairs
gig. And these other people came we went
down into the basement and put
a bar across the door and it is pretty
strong How could we possibly get away from
here let us child who really want to
call in each other and as we would enter
a certain place and somebody wants their
view or Nash Dr Grimes your entire staff I
know has been working very hard to find
some solution to these things that are
happening have any answers. Yes we have
some answers but first let me stress the
importance of seeking medical attention for
anyone who's been injured in any way we
don't know yet what complications might
result from such change how that was
a kid been hurt. So. You could argue
until you know Julie you tell Judy to come
up here and you stay with the kid all
right. In the call room at the university
we have
a cadaver doctor from which all four limbs
and then if you take some time early
this morning to open his eyes he began
to move which truck it was dead but it
opened his eyes and tried to move.
The watch upstairs and she asked for
me she had. Better understand. Baby.
Mommy. Comeback.
Thank you Jimmy. The body should be disposed
of and watch actually by cremation how
much after death and body
becomes reaction only
a matter. Of trying to make any real You're
right it doesn't give them time to make
you all right. To be carried to the
street and burn they must be burned
amid soaking with gasoline and
burned. By the four golden years
comforted
a funeral service will get. There
just dead and danged. Huge And
finally there is or is there she's the
chair in the small strips OK Is there
a better yes we need some bottles or Joram
a box of crackers all always
try to escape hey this is
a can of kerosene on it asking about our
outlook for the bottles so maybe queueing
down there or maybe you keep the gas pump
on I'll check. Carville's from window
upstairs meantime kind of try to guess
you come back for the rest of the people
that leave the door open someplace.
Very This door was close to the truck.
Before all this is live along the rest of
you can all up in there are from stars in
the south and there's
a key on here this label from the gas pump
out back. Not really there you see the
frog I found that. I can trust no sweat.
You really. Mean.
So if you Google whatever law we
find Gonzalo go. You go. Away go
talk you out don't go to the store
or you thought of probably was
a bad hour in lot of the store so
toward the back and. We get the
gas and go back in the house when you know
the big worry about getting everybody
into the drug. Was moving.
Many.
You know he says now for me. He's
now the town the town. I'm in
Canton. Community we moved.
Tunisian about the Sunni stand out
only get this recorded message. I
can only call the folks that are going to
be so worried about us. Everything on the
right since we get to will it will
call them they might even visit.
Towns. I usually get in the right thing
to worry about getting out of here.
One of the television says that's the
right thing to do with got to get to the
rescue station I don't know c'mon and
you're starting to sound like Mr Cooper and
why do you have to go there I know how to
handle that truck and I can handle the
pump and isn't anything about it stuff.
We're safe in here for home loan
money we're safe now but it's going to
be more and more of those things I did I
know all of. This.
Member only had to dig sled limit how
difficult it was tries to convince you that
it was right to leave a number member
we had to go to Willard then this isn't
a passing thing honey. It's not like just
a wee passing through we've
got to do something fast.
I just don't want you to go that's
a whole day. And. We said.
Why. Should we use it only.
Because we're to do any
new.
We bury her downstairs we have
to go downstairs. She's right
good out just where do we get. If
we could all be oh I'd like to
leave Yes thanks.
Good luck. Getting.
There every day.
Live.
Live. Live.
Live
. Live.
live
Live.
Live
.
Still.
Lead.
Slim
. Live.
Little.
Lives.
Come on.
Lead.
Live
live.
.
No.
Luck.
The thing has.
The the ear.
It's not really
a clock and. There's supposed to be
another broadcast at three
o'clock ten minutes oh only ten
minutes we don't have very
long to waste but you leave.
Oh he's busy soon. It's
ten minutes to trade.
You know everything about this area all
I mean is were the nearest town I had
out. We were.
Just trying to get to
a motel before dark. So those things turned
to cold to go back on the trails and
drive where it seems like
a street car. Seems like
a hand. Forget it it's at least
a mile Johnny has the keys we're going to
carry that Chalo mile through that army
of things up there I can carry it.
But Charlotte sure one of those
things grabbed her that are on the
arm what's wrong who knows what
kind of disease those things carry Is she
conscious barely she can't walk she's
too weak. Well one of us to
try to get to the car even to
turn it over by yourself you can't
start the car Johnny has the keys.
You have
a car where where is. Your stuff yeah
yeah I know but where is it. The
. Good Lord.
Being monitored closely by scientists at
all the radiation detection stations at
this hour they report the level of the
mysterious radiation continues to increase
steadily so long as the situation remains
government spokesman warns that dead
bodies will continue to be transformed
into the flesh eating groups all versions
will be John I doing this crisis from
whatever caused come back to life to seek
human victims unless their bodies are first
just posed by cremation or news cameras
have just returned from covering such
a search and destroy operation against
this one conducted by share of Qana
McClelland in Butler County Pennsylvania
now let's go to that film before kick all
law enforcement agencies and the military
has been organized to search out and
destroy the marauding Google's survival
command center at the Pentagon has
disclosed that it can be killed
by a shot in the head or
a heavy blow to the Skulk officials are
quoted as explaining that since the brain
of
a Google has been activated by the radiation
the plan is kill the brain and you kill
the ghoul. Where they were the
supplier I guess now we're all right.
There are. Far we don't want to get not
but again. Chief Chief McClellan has
everything going things are
going to bad men are taking
a pretty good you want to get on the other
side of the road over there are she do
you think we'll be able to defeat these
things well we kill nineteen of them today
right in this area that was last three we
caught trying to claw their way into an
abandoned shed they musta thought somebody
was in there there were no we are to
make an hour kind of noise
we came over and being
a mob blasted him down. Yeah OK Chief
if I were surrounded by six or eight
of these things would I stand
a chance with them well
there's no problem if you had
a gun shoot them in the head that's
a sure way to kill them if you
don't get yourself a club or
a torch beat them or burn and they go up
pretty well Chief McLellan Alan do you
think it will take you until you get the
situation under control well it's pretty
hard to say we don't know how many we know
when we find him we can kill him. Are
they slow moving chief Yeah they're dead
they're all messed up well in time would
you say you had to be able to wrap this
up in twenty four hours Well we don't
really know we know will be end to it most
of the night probably end of the early
morning we're working our way toward Wellard
and we're team up with the National
Guard over there and then
we'll be able to give
a more definite view thank you very much
shape McCall and this is Bill Cargill W.-I
see T.V.
Eleven News thank you Bill for that report.
Official spokesman declined to speculate
just how long it may take to kill off the
flesh eaters Sean was the heavy rain.
The fuse box in the
cellar I don't know why.
It isn't
a fuse the problems are now. Hell I
have to get that done. And to
have enough but two people are
dead already on account of that guy take
a look out that window. He
.
Says.
It's. The least.
The air.
OK. Look.
OK. OK.
OK. I get it.
Live
live live
live live.
Live. Live.
Live.
Live. Live
live
.
Live
live.
live Live.
Live
. It has.
Been.
He.
The E.U.
.
Now want to get about four or five man
a couple of dogs here behind those tree
and want to go check it out and you tell
yourself yes you are going to stay with
them till we meet up with the National
Guard or to get out while the volunteers
are doing all the work you take back where
we should be wrapped up here about three
or four more hours we're propping it in
the lower jam I guess you can call it Army
National Guard NEC university and I want
to come with me. So the Mexican officer
tapped All right Steve tell him we're going
to stay with them. Everything
appears to be under control.
Us.
Than ever.
Did you manage. Somebody at
a cookout event noise sure looks like it.
Isn't fair that not only Steve you
want to get out that film doesn't
go on far.
You drag him throw it on a far
nothing down here I go down
a good man go check out that
there's something I heard
a noise. I'm getting
hit right between
a. Good shot OK he's dead let's
go get him that's another one sort of far.
I think.
Zero.